

CONTACT ME AT

- Office Address: Usilova Ul., bld. 7, appt. 60, Nizhniy Novgorod
- angel126mic@gmail.com
- https://angel126mic.github.io/
- S live:.cid.73fdab2ba11aac7b

SKILLS SUMMARY

★★★★☆ React

★★★★ Javascrip

★★★★☆ Node

★★★☆☆ Vue

★★★★☆ PH

★★★★ HTML & CSS

★★★★☆ Assembly Language

★★★☆☆ Java

**** C/C++

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Ural Federal University

B.A, Computer & Technology | September 2012 –
June 2016

- Operating Systems
 Architecture
- Linux/Unix Programming
- Assembly Language
- Usability in Website and Software Design
- C++ Programming I & Damp; II
- Web Page Development
- Relational Database Design & Design
- Data Engineering, Advanced Software Programming.

ANGEL MIC

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

With 8+ years of experience in creating and delivering user-friendly applications and solutions, I look forward to bringing my strong creative, technical, and analytical skills.

Throughout my career, I have been acknowledged as a solution-focused professional with the ability to develop innovative applications using advanced technologies. In my current role as a Full-stack Developer, I collaborate closely with the international team to develop and implement 30+ full-stack web applications, ensuring optimal functionality, quality, and reliability.

WORK EXPERIENCE

ITO Creative Solutions | Web Developer, Remote Work October 2012 – June 2016

- Improved legacy front end by replacing it with AngularJS, Rest API, Laravel. (Resulted into 50% faster loading times).
- Worked with a team of 6+ people, developers, QA and scrum masters.

Genuine Technology | Manager, Remote work July 2016 - October 2019

- Gained hands-on expertise in Vue.js & Duxt, React, N Redux, Bootstrap, Foundation, Express and similar backend Node.js as well as front-end presentation frameworks web application frameworks.
- Various react native & amp; ionic application development.
- Conducted unit and load testing for high profile customer facing applications, which reduced system failure rate by 70%
- Management With Trello and Roadmunk

Self Employed | Freelancer(Web, Software)

February 2020 -

- Develop full-stack web applications to analyze and process data for different clients with Laravel, Symfony, Node.js, Typescript, Vue and React, SQL
- Building software applications using C/C++, C#, Java, Qt and Assembly Language
- Reversing Engineer for application and apks.